<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KiloBite</string>
    <string name="goal_weight">Goal Weight</string>
    <string name="current_weight">Current Weight(lbs)</string>
    <string name="current_height">Current Height(in)</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Get my Workouts!</string>
    <string name="change_goals">Update Goals</string>
    <string name="show_subtitle">Show Subtitle</string>
    <string name="hide_subtitle">Hide Subtitle</string>
    <string name="glossary">Glossary</string>
    <string name="exercise_descriptions">BEAR CRAWL:
-Get down on all fours with your arms straight, hands below your shoulders, and
your knees bent 90 degrees below your hips (only your hands and toes should be
touching the ground)
-While keeping your back flat, crawl forward and backward moving opposite
hands and feet in unison (right hand and left foot/ left hand and right foot)
\n
 BROAD JUMP:
-Place your feet shoulder-width apart
-Keep your toes pointed straight
-Stretch up with your arms and rise up onto the balls of your feet with your hips
extended
-Bring your arms back behind you and bend your knees and hips
-Drive as powerfully as possible off of the ground while simultaneously throwing
your arms forward as forcefully as possible.
-Once you are airborne, extend your hips up and out and throw your feet forward
(this will add momentum to the jump, keeping you in the air longer)
-Land flatfooted with your weight slightly forward. You must stick the landing and
not fall backward or forward, and your hands cannot touch the ground at any time
after landing.
\n
        BURPEES:
-Begin in a standing position
- Move into a squat position with your hands on the ground
- Kick your feet back into a plank position, while keeping your arms extended
- Immediately return your feet into squat position.
- Stand up from the squat position
\n
        CLOSE-GRIP PUSH-UPS:
-Lay down on the ground face down
        -Make a diamond with your hands on the ground, or simply bring your hands
together within the distance between your shoulders
-For each repetition, use your chest and arms to push yourself up from the ground
- At the top of the repetition, let your torso fall back to the rest position without
letting your chest touch the ground
\n
        DIPS:
- Locate the dip/raise machine
-Grab the bars and jump up (balance yourself with locked elbows)
-Lower your body by bending your arms (lean your torso slightly forward)
-Go down until your shoulders are below your elbows at the bottom
-Lift your body back up to the starting position by straightening your arms
-Balance yourself with your shoulders over your hands (lock your elbows)
\n
FLUTTER KICKS(LEG):
Lie on your back with your legs extended and your arms alongside your hips
(palms down)
 Lift your legs 4 to 6 inches off of the floor (press your lower back into the
mat/floor)
Keep your legs straight as you rhythmically raise one leg higher, then switch
(move in a fluttering, up and down motion)
\n
GLUTE-BRIDGES:
-Lie face-down on the floor, with your knees bent and feet flat on the ground, or
with your heels in contact with a stable, elevated surface
-Keep your arms at your side with your elbows and shoulders flat against the
ground to help brace your upper body
-For each repetition, lift your hips up off the ground until your knees, hips, and
shoulders form a straight line and hold the position for 2-3 seconds before slowly
easing yourself down.
\n

KNEE-RAISES:

- Locate the dip/raise machine
-Put your back against the pad, and hold your body up by resting your arms/hands
on the parallel bars
- Allow your legs to dangle and then slowly lift your knees toward your chest. The
motion should be controlled and deliberate as you bring your knees up until your
thighs are parallel to the floor
- Return your legs to the starting position, letting them down slowly.
        \n
LUNGES(LEG):
-Keep your upper body straight, with your shoulders back and relaxed and chin up
(pick a point to stare at in front of you so you don’t keep looking down)
-Step forward with one leg, lowering your hips until both knees are bent at about a
90-degree angle
-Make sure your front knee is directly above your ankle (not pushed out too far),
and make sure your other knee doesn’t touch the floor
-Keep the weight in your heels as you push back up to the starting position
\n

MOUNTAIN CLIMBERS:
-Start in a plank position with your arms and legs straightened.
-Keep your abs pulled in and your body straight.
-Squeeze your glutes and pull your shoulders away from your ears
-Pull your right knee into your chest.  As the knee draws to the chest, pull your abs
in even tighter to be sure your body doesn’t sag or come out of its plank position.
- Quickly switch and pull the left knee in. At the same time you push your right leg
back, pull your left knee in to the chest using the same form
-Continue to switch knees. Pull the knees in right, left, and right, left — always
switching simultaneously so that you are using a “running” motion.
-As you begin to move more quickly be in constant awareness of your body
position and be sure to keep a straight line in your spine and don’t let your head
droop
\n
PULL-UPS:
-Hang from a pull-up bar with hands facing away from body and feet off the
ground
- Using your shoulders and arms, lift yourself up until your chin is above the bar
-Release back to a normal hang with shoulder blades level and apart
\n
PUSH-UPS:
-Lay down on the ground face down
-Set your hands on the floor at a slightly larger distance apart from the length of
the distance of your shoulders
-For each repetition, use your chest and arms to push yourself up from the ground
-At the top of the repetition, let your torso fall back to the rest position without
letting your chest touch the ground
\n
SIT-UPS:
-Lie on your back with your arms crossed over your chest
-Keep your feet flat on the ground and your knees bent
-For each repetition, raise your torso using your abdominals until your elbows
meet your knees or thighs
-Let your torso gently fall back to the ground
\n
SQUATS:
\nStand with your feet facing forward about shoulder length apart and your chest
and shoulders up
\nFor each repetition, Look straight ahead and, while keeping your back straight,
lower your body using your knees and leg muscles
\nBe sure to keep your knees in line with your feet and keep your feet straight and
flat
\nOnce your glutes are lowered to as close to your knee level as they can go,
straighten your knees and raise yourself back up to rest position
\n
V-UPS:
-Lie on your back with your arms raised over your head straight out and your legs
extended straight out on the floor
-Keep your knees and elbows straight throughout your repetitions
-For each repetition, raise both your legs and torso simultaneously straight up until
your hands meet your toes and your glutes are the only thing touching the ground
-Hold this position for one count, or a second, and then gently let your legs and
back fall back to rest position
</string>
</resources>
